Sorry, that was embarrassing.
You don't have to say sorry,
okay?
You have nothing to do
with this.
It's between me and Andrew.
Yeah, I know.
I have nothing to do
with your real relationship.
Are you jealous?
Me? Jealous?
No way.
Let's talk about this later.
Someone might see us.
I'll see you tomorrow, Clarissa.
I like her.
I hope she doesn't give up
easily.
Then be nice to her.
Hey, what are you peeking at?
I'm not planning to steal
anything here.
Enough talk!
[GRUNTING AND GROANING]
I said I don't want trouble!
What are you doing?
My companion went missing,
so I was going to bring this
to the room.
I thought you left me.
I have a question for you.
Madam Delilah,
what do you do for her?
Maybe I can apply for a job
with your boss.
Tomorrow, I'll introduce you
to my boss.
That's a promis, okay?
- I'm sorry.
- Why are you apologizing?
You don't have to apologize.
If you two get back together,
then go ahead.
I want something different now.
There you are!
How are my two lovebirds?
We'll treat you to dinner.
I have to decline
because I have a very important
meeting tomorrow night.
I'm sure Berdugo is the one
Delilah's meeting with.
Let's talk about this tomorrow.
There's still time.
I'm really sleepy.
I thought you weren't mad at me
anymore?
Why does it hurt?
We're not even together.
I don't want you anymore.
Why am I affected?
Would I be happy
if we get back together?
I already know
what will make me happy.
[OBB]
Don't worry, Boss.
I'll take care
of my fellow officers.
I'll make sure your service
to me is rewarded.
Oh, Sir...
Ma'am Delilah is expecting you.
Your villa is ready.
Boss, just follow my car, okay?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
So, Boss?
I'll come back tomorrow morning.
Okay.
Make sure nothing goes wrong
tomorrow, okay?
Yes, Boss.
But Matias mentioned
someone's been asking about you.
Is that true?
Who?
Have you met them?
That's the problem, Boss,
I didn't recognize them.
But if ever I do recognize them,
I'll definitely know
who they are for sure.
All right, Boss, I'll go ahead.
[CAR REVVING]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MOTORCYCLE REVVING]
[PHONE RINGING]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Joey?
Dad?
Finally, I am able
to see your face, Joey.
How are you? I've missed you.
Where's your mother?
Did you tell her?
I'll talk to her.
Dad, mom's not here right now.
Where is she?
I'm sorry, Dad, but...
I haven't gone home yet.
What?
Where are you?
Joey?
Who is that?
Is that Andrew?
Joey, your father's alive?
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
This is why I can move
freely now...
because the syndicate thinks
I'm dead.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Honestly, this might be
the wildest
yet smartest undercover strat
I've ever witnessed
in my entire journalism career.
I can't believe this.
Hey, you talk about
my dad's situation
like it's a news article.
It's not like that.
I just can't believe it.
I mean, of course,
I had to understand everything
because I want to help your dad.
That's exactly why we're here,
right?
You know, to be honest...
you shouldn't be doing this.
You're not supposed to be there.
You should go home.
You might get in trouble.
It's dangerous.
Dad, I've done this many times.
I agree, but it's still
dangerous.
Major...
You're right.
But Joey is doing a good job.
She's sharp, resourceful,
and she knows how to fight.
But I promise you,
just like before,
I won't let anything
happen to her.
[PLEASANT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ROOSTER CROWING]
Auntie Bebeng, that's your
fifth snack already.
You'll finish all our snacks
if you keep eating like that.
Why are you kids meddling
with everything, even my snacks.
Why don't you ask yourself
if there's anything left
for you?
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
You think I don't know
why you suddenly came home?
You're probably running away
from someone...
in Manila. Right?
But, Peter, how are you really?
I'm okay, Auntie Beng.
I'll forget eventually.
That's not true.
You even dreamed about her.
Wait.
Does that mean if my crush
dreams about me,
she's in love with me too?
There, that's where
you're good at.
You, young people,
have such shallow
perspective of love.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
When you're not chosen,
that's it, it's the end
of the world for you.
You change your looks,
you change yourself.
That's not how life works.
Wow.
Coming from you, Auntie Bebeng,
who's single for life?
You, rascal!
Hey, don't underestimate me.
Before I decided
to be single forever,
I experienced all of that, okay?
Been there, done that.
So don't disparage me
with your love talk.
- [SCOFFS]
- [PLAYFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[KEYBOARD CLICKING]
Is your keyboard working?
Of course, why?
So, you can keep the sound down.
Sorry.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Well, it's just that,
I just can't believe
Major Delgado is still alive...
and still an undercover,
no less.
You really are father
and daughter...
you're both certified
never-say-die.
The way you said it,
it's like we're bad people.
And...
[PLAYFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
It's really like that,
when you want something...
you'll do everything to get it.
I'm sure it's not just me
and my dad who are like that.
Hello? There are plenty
of people...
who can't move on.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Wait, is this...
about Zoey?
Is this because...
she kissed me out of nowhere?
[PLAYFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PLINKS]
- [FIZZING]
- [UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
It dissolves fast, Madam.
That means the stimulant's
purity is high.
This is good, Madam.
Good.
The kids will love this...
it hits fast.
I'm looking forward to our
shipment later.
And I look forward
to the five hundred million.
[LAUGHS]
Oh, by the way,
as for transport,
my man here, Francis,
has already secured the route.
And apparently...
one of our brave policemen
in Valmora is already
on our payroll.
A pleasant surprise,
Captain Castro.
Thank you, Madam!
I'll take care of
my fellow officers.
And as for those following
Berdugo,
we will neutralize them
before they get close.
Following?
You mean you have active
threats?
Just some small-time
competition.
Hardly worth my attention.
[DAUNTING MUSIC PLAYING]
I've heard about you
for a long time, Berdugo.
And today, I'll finally meet you
and see if you're actually
worth the fear
that follows your name.
But let me be clear...
if something goes wrong
with this deal,
your Lumen-X will be history
in Valmora.
Don't forget, Delilah...
you're just a distributor.
I am the creator.
I have the labs,
while you only have your men.
While you do business
in your small province,
I'm already conquering
the entire country.
Don't get too comfortable
because I am not a gentleman.
I'm not the type to hold back
just because you're a woman.
[DAUNTING MUSIC CONTINUES]
The chief is just waiting
for the medico legal's answer.
They said they still need
to double-check.
Double-check?
My husband's body has been
with them for so long.
What else do they need?
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Cruz, be honest with me.
Will we still see Miguel's body?
Will I still be able
to hold a wake for my husband?
I'm sorry, Ma'am.
There's just a process
we must follow.
We'll talk later.
Ma'am, I'm sorry...
I woke you up
because of my loud voice.
It's okay.
But did I hear it right?
You still can't hold a wake
for your husband?
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
That's what you think,
but she's not the one
I'm talking about.
Okay, fine. Let's say...
it's her.
Is it a red flag if...
I get back together with her?
Is that desperate?
That's up to you.
It's your choice,
whatever feels right for you.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
But do you want me to...
feel that way about her?
Why are you asking
so many questions?
If that's what you want,
then go ahead.
As for me, I've got different
priorities here in Valmora.
Not your love life.
Fine, chill.
But I hope...
I hope we accomplish
our mission,
so we can both go home
without anyone bothering us
anymore.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DOOR CREAKS]
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey...
[KNOCKS]
Hey, we had an agreement,
remember?
I always use the bathroom first!
Come on, get out of there!
- You were taking too long!
- You're so hard to deal with!
Wait, I'll be quick.
And you're lying down...
you're not even looking at me.
You always want to have it
your way.
[PLEASANT MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey!
Nice smile.
Are you talking to your crush?
Yes, Peter,
I'm chatting with her now.
Wow, you're leveling up.
She said she's just busy,
that's why she hasn't replied.
She's got a lot going on
at school.
She's in every org.
That means she's active.
That's amazing.
That's why I like her.
She's smart and responsible.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Just like Joey...
smart, responsible,
loving to her family.
Even though it's dangerous now,
she takes the risk for them.
It's hard to fall in love
with someone like that, Peter.
You got lots of competition
for her attention.
Peter, let me ask you...
did Joey really tell you
she doesn't like you?
No, but it feels that way.
Because she doesn't pay
attention
to any of the interest
I'm showing her.
Nothing.
Are you sure?
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
Didn't you just say
she's facing great danger
for her family?
Maybe she has bigger problems
to deal with,
so she doesn't have time
for other things.
So, listen, both of you...
Always remember...
a person who truly loves,
never gets tired of waiting.
Okay? Okay? Okay?
Me, I've been waiting
for 48 years, still nothing.
Life!
[PLEASANT MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey, Keith, come here,
help me out!
All right!
We need to add more people.
Five hundred million
is at stake here.
We can't afford to be
at a disadvantage.
Francis...
- Hi.
- Zoey.
Are you busy? I was hoping
to invite you to dinner.
I felt our last conversation
was cut short,
- you know.
- Oh, dinner?
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Sorry, I can't.
How about lunch?
- Lunch?
- Are you free for lunch?
[CLICKS TONGUE]
I've got a lot to do too,
I'm sorry, Zoey...
but Madam Delilah needs me.
That's too bad.
You're always so busy.
Sometimes I feel like
you're not really
the owner of this resort.
Why do you say that?
Because the resort owners
I know...
are chill.
[DAUNTING MUSIC PLAYING]
But you, you handle
everything yourself.
I'm just very hands-on, Zoey.
But I have something
to tell you.
Zoey, I'm interested in you.
I want to change.
Change?
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Wow, I'm glad you left
some for me.
Only one left?
[PLAYFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Delicious.
- What?
- Let me.
See? You're not even listening
to anything.
It was paused!
You heard me,
but you still took
the last longganisa .
Oh, come on.
I was hungry.
That was good for four...
you made it good for one.
I said I was hungry!
Wait, what's your problem?
I'm hungry, that's all.
Joey, is there
a problem between us?
What's your deal?
I don't get you.
My husband's death
was so sudden.
And now, we don't even know
if we can hold a wake
for Miguel.
I'm sorry you're going
through this.
[SIGHS]
How I wish I could
actually help you.
Back when I was...
the queen of headlines,
maybe I could.
But now, here.
I'm the queen of the headboard.
Bedridden royalty.
[CHUCKLES]
I'm sorry, Ma'am.
I didn't...
I didn't mean to laugh.
It's okay, it's okay.
I wanted you to laugh.
Earlier, when I saw your anger,
your frustration, your grief...
I knew it hurt more...
than my illness.
Maybe that's how it is.
We all carry our own burdens.
Exactly.
So, what's your plan now?
I don't know yet.
But Sir Tomas told me
he wants to help
with Miguel's drug case.
Maybe I should talk
to Sir Tomas.
No!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
You don't need Tomas's help.
Do not deal with him.
And no matter what promises
he makes,
no matter what help he says
he can give...
do not take it.
Ma'am, why?
What's going on with Sir Tomas?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Wow!
Our sweet patient is awake.
You look startled.
Did something happen?
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
No, nothing.
It's just that...
Clarissa, she told me
a little ghost story.
I was surprised by the ending.
I didn't expect it.
Mom, stress is off limits.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
The doctor was clear
about that, right?
Yes.
I'm fine, I'm fine.
Is it time for me
to take a bath?
Oh, yes.
Since Clarissa is new,
I'll walk her through
the routine, okay?
- Okay.
Clarissa, let's do this.
Okay, Mom.
- Yes.
- Okay, hold on.
[GRUNTS]
Slowly.
There you go.
Slippers.
Here, here.
Okay.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
I want to change.
Change?
Change my life.
I want to have a family.
I want to have children.
But not here,
I want to be far away from here.
That's why I need to finish
this last...
Last what?
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Investment.
It's quite huge, and...
the transaction
is scheduled for later.
But, Zoey, after that,
I want a new life.
[LAUGHS]
Wow, you're moving too fast!
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
We've only been on one date.
We just met.
Anyway...
Have you spoken
to Madam Delilah?
Did you tell her
I want to work for her?
About that?
Sure, I'll tell her.
Thank you.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Joey, come on, let's go.
Where?
Why are we here?
To look for evidence,
information,
for the mission.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Shouldn't Zoey
be with you for that?
I might just get in the way.
You know, last night,
it was cute
that you were affected.
But now...
you're insecure.
Excuse me!
Me, insecure?
Why would I be insecure?
You can't move on from Zoey.
I don't need to move on...
there's no issue for me.
You can marry her,
have kids with her.
That's not an issue for me.
I don't care.
So, go ahead.
Whatever, Joey.
If you don't come with me,
I won't tell your father...
if we get information.
You're the only one
who can contact him.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
When do I meet your business
partner, Berdugo?
You do not meet him
whenever you want.
I didn't agree to join here
just to be a nobody.
But since it's official
and government sanctioned,
civilians are not allowed...
I have it filed,
it's documented.
You didn't.
You're leaving,
and you'll leave me
with some guy I haven't
even spoken to?
My father needs to know
about the transaction.
You know what I smell?
The people looking for you.
Are they your problem?
We had an agreement.
Honor that agreement.